bsrunner.com 2019-06-01

# Bayshore Projects

BayShore Projects Co. Ltd. and its affiliates (“BayShore”, “we”, “us”, “our”) are committed to the protection of the personal data you may share on our website. The following Privacy Policy discloses the information gathering, sharing, and safe-guarding practices for the www.bayshoreprojects.com website (“BayShore Website”, “The Website”, or “Website”). 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and forms part of, The Website’s Terms and Conditions. A link to these Terms and Conditions is located at the bottom of each page of The Website. By using the BayShore Website you are accepting the Terms and Conditions and therefore also agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you must not use The Website. Your use of this Website signifies your understanding and acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

We may collect the following types of personal information in order to provide you with the use and access to The Website, services and tools, and for any additional purposes set out in this 

**Privacy Policy:**

Name, and contact information, such as email address, phone number, mobile telephone number, physical address, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as bank account numbers;

transactional information based on your activities on the sites including, but not limited to reserving property, committing to buy property, buying, selling, paying, billing, generating content, providing content, and other information you may provide;

personal information you provide to us through correspondence, chats, dispute resolution, or shared by you from other social applications, services or websites;  
additional personal information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself if we believe you are violating site policies (for example, we may ask you to send us an ID to answer additional questions online to help verify your identity);

information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising, including, but not limited to, device ID, device type, geo-location information, computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information.

Aggregate Information: BayShore collects non-identifying, general, generic and aggregate information to better design our Website and services. 

Non-Personal Information: BayShore may collect non-personal information as you use BayShore. When you use the site, BayShore, third-party service providers (e.g. Google Analytics), and partners may receive and record non-personal information from cookies, server logs, and similar technology from your browser or mobile device, including your IP address. 

We may combine some Non-Personal Information with the Personal Information we collect. Where we do so, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information if the resulting combination may be used to readily identify or locate you in the same manner as Personal Information alone. 

2\. How do we store your information?

We use various hosting service providers; therefore your information may be transferred to and stored on servers in various locations around the world. We protect your information using technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorised access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the safeguards we employ directly or through our service providers include firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to our data centres, and information access authorisation controls. 

3\. How do we use your Information?

When you use the BayShore site, we may request certain information. BayShore does not share any of your personally identifiable or transactional information with any person or entity, other than as set out in this policy. No other third party receives your personally identifiable information or other transactional data except for those with whom you have transactions and share that information. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web site, used to notify consumers about updates to our web site and for communications, such as customer service. 

Communications: We may send you a welcome email to verify your account and other transactional emails for operational purposes, such as billing, account management, or system maintenance. You may only stop those emails by terminating your account. We may also send you promotions, project and/or product announcements, surveys, newsletters, updates, evaluations, and event information or other marketing or commercial e-mails. You can opt out of receiving these email communications from BayShore at any time by unsubscribing using the unsubscribe link within each email, updating your e-mail preferences on your BayShore account or emailing us to have your contact information removed from our email list or registration database. 

Marketing: You agree that we may use your personal information to tell you about our products and services, deliver targeted marketing and promotional offers based on your communication preferences, and to customise, measure, and improve our advertising. You can unsubscribe from emails at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in the email. 

We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or non- affiliated companies for marketing purposes (including direct marketing purposes) without your permission. We may use and share Non-Personal Information for our marketing purposes, including, without limitation, marketing on other websites. For example, we may use the information to control the number of times you have seen an ad, deliver ads tailored to your interests, and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. You can prevent us from tailoring our ads to you on other websites by deleting your cookies (see below). 

4\. Sharing your Information

We disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. As stated above, we do not disclosure your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.   
We may share aggregate data with advertisers and other third parties. BayShore uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer and transaction data exchanged with our site. 

5\. Cookies

Cookies are pieces of data assigned by a web server that uniquely identify the browser on your PC. BayShore uses cookies called "persistent" cookies to enable the site to remember you on subsequent visits, speeding up or enhancing your experience of services or functions offered. Cookies also enable our systems to gather information about your navigational patterns through the site. You have the option to disable cookies at any time through your browsers. We may also store your website activity in cookies which may be used by third party vendors, such as Google, to serve ads based on your behaviour on our website.   
The third party vendors may receive and record non-personal information from cookies, server logs, and similar technology from your browser or mobile device, including your IP address. You may opt out of their use of cookies by visiting the relevant opt-out page. BayShore will endeavor to provide all applicable links to do so. 

If you access our Services with your login credentials from a social networking site (e.g., Facebook or Twitter) or if you otherwise agree to associate your BayShore account with a social networking account, we may receive personal information about you from such social networking site, in accordance with the terms of use and privacy policy of the social networking site. For example, Facebook may share with us your friend list, birthday, information about the interests of you or your friends or other personal information, in order to help us establish your account, tailor services to you and find other current or potential site users that you know. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via other aspects of the Site. You are also subject to the social networking site's terms of use and privacy policy. We use the OAuth (open authorization) protocol to enable us to access this information without collecting your password when you agree allow another application to access your account information. 

6\. Accessing and updating your Information

If we offer an account to you, you can update your information through your account profile settings. If you have any concerns about the accuracy of your information or any privacy complaints please contact us at webmaster@bayshoreprojects.com.

7\. Privacy Policy Modification

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Therefore visitors are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.
